(Howard:)Ma, Ma, calm down.
(Howard:)Listen to me.
(Howard:)I know it says click
with the mouse,
(Howard:)but on a laptop,
the trackpad is the mouse.
(Howard:)Now, put your finger on it.
(Howard:)Doesn't matter which finger.
(Howard:)Good choice.
(Howard:)Now move it down
to your e-mail icon.
(Howard:)Yeah, the little envelope.
(Howard:)What do you mean,
"What does it look like?"
(Howard:)It looks like an envelope!
(Howard:)Fine, you don't like
the computer,
(Howard:)don't use it!
(Howard:)Sure, we can exchange it
for a salad spinner. Good-bye!
(Raj:)That's a Hanukkah present
you're regretting, huh?
(Sheldon:)I won't say that
all senior citizens
(Sheldon:)who can't master technology
should be publicly flogged,
(Sheldon:)but if we made an
example of one or two,
(Sheldon:)it might give the others
incentive to try harder.
(Leonard:)I had a great idea.
(Leonard:)You know how
we're always having
(Leonard:)to stop and solve
differential equations,
(Leonard:)like when you're doing
Fourier analysis,